This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Initial
Raise up your hands 高く [Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
Raise up your hands takaku
(Everybody now te wo agero saa)
Tsukame brand new tomorrow
掴め Brand new tomorrow [You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
風の中で 自分を知る ずっと最高のDreamだろう
Kaze no naka de jibun wo shiru
Zutto zekkei no dream darou
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh raise up you can't stop
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Ikiteru dake de marumouke nara ganbarouze marugoto ittennbari
生きてるだけで何やろうかな
Gamble on 迫る鼓動にテンバリ
同じMission 同じ一生
Onaji mission, onaji isshou
Dondake yume atsuika ga shobu darou
どんだけ夢熱いかが勝負だろ
Escalator nashi no eien
Escalator 無しの永遠
Ashi koshi kitae reruze yeah, yeah
足腰鍛え Let's begin yeah
Douse noboru kaidan
どうせのぼる階段
心こっちにCustomizeしちゃえばいい
Kokoro kocchi ni customize shichaeba ii
Kezurarete sugiru mainichi
削られて 過ぎる毎日[But you know]
Kezurarete sugiru mainichi (But you know ?)
攻めがいのあるGameと 笑い飛ばして
Semegai no aru game to warai tobashite
Let's see how fast you can do it
Let's see how fast you can do it.
Raise up your hands ずっと
[Everybody gonna tell you I can't stop]
Raise up your hands zutto
(Everybody now te wo agero saa)
Hashire sleepless challenger
走れ Sleepless challenger [You don't stop]
(You don't stop)
今に生きる 理由を探す
Ima ni ikiru riyuu sagasu
Yume tsukinai quest
夢尽きないQuest
(Let's go)
Oh[Let's go] Oh[Let's go]
Oh
Oh (Let's go)
Oh, raise up your hands now.
Oh raise up you can't stop
霧
Fog...?!
I can't see anything...
見えない 何も
A white void !
白い闇だ
Incoming call...
着信あり  目標エリアに対向車なし
...which means no oncoming
traffic in the target area.
Nice Kenta. Perfect timing.
ナイス ケンタ ジャスタイミング
Full throttle in these conditions...?!
駄目  この状況でアクセル全開は
That's impossible for a human.
人としてはありえない
Cleared the fog, and visibility is back.
抜けた 視界が戻った
I lost.
負けた なんてヤツだ
What a guy.
That was so splendid that for some
reason I smile before feeling the frustration.
鮮やか過ぎて悔しいと思う前に
なぜか笑えてしまう
If someone can pull that off,
there's nothing you can do.
そこまでやられちゃしかたない
想像を絶するパフォーマンス  完敗だ プロジェクトD
Your performance is
beyond my imagination.
It's my total defeat, Project D.
White Demon
Keisuke...
啓介さん やりましたね
You did it !
Yeah.
ああ
It worked out well, Kenta.
うまくいったぜ ケンタ
だけど 肝冷やしましたよ
I was scared to death.
The fog was thicker than expected,
and I was so anxious while I was waiting.
思ったより霧が濃くて 待ってるこっちのほうはもう気が気じゃなかったっすよ
When your FD burst
out from that white fog...
真っ白な霧の中から  どんと啓介さんのFDが飛び出してきた時は
...I was so thrilled that
I had tears in my eyes.
しんそこ痺れたっていうか 本当に目に涙浮かべましたよ
Keisuke came up with the idea of
where and how to make his move.
今回の作戦 どこでどう仕掛けるかは
啓介が自分で考えたんだ
I gave him some hints, but I
didn't give him any concrete advice.
俺は材料を与えただけで 具体的なアドバイスはほとんど何もしていない
Is that right ?
そうなのか いや 本当に成長してるよ 啓介は
You've really grown, Keisuke.
Aren't you saying the same
thing after every battle ?
バトル終わるたびにいつも同じこと言うけど
That's what I think every time,
so it can't be helped.
毎回思うんだが  しょうがないよ
ハイスピード区間で仕掛けたのは見事だったな
It was incredible that you made your
move in the high-speed segment.
あの区間は途中でS字にカーブしていて 単純な直線じゃないし
That segment has an S-curve,
so it's not a simple straightaway.
I'm impressed that you
kept the throttle open.
よくアクセルを踏み切れたな
まっ 時間かけてリハーサルやったし
I spent a lot of time on rehearsal, and the
usual blind training must have helped, too.
いつもやってる ブラインドトレー二ングのおかげだろうな
Still, the fear of not
being able to see is strong.
それでも 見えないことの恐怖はすごい
I couldn't have stepped on the gas unless
I was sure there'd be no oncoming car.
対向車が絶対にいないという確信がなければ 踏めなかったよ
My temples are still throbbing.
こめかみの辺りがまだずきずきするぜ
I must have really exceeded
the limits of my concentration.
集中力をキープできる限界をとっくに超えていたんだな
I tired myself out by building up the pace in the fog.
霧の中でペースを作り続けてることで一気に消耗してしまったんだ
In the end, I didn't have
enough mental strength.
最後は気力が残っていなかった
Maybe this is the result of the
difference in our fighting spirit.
結果的には闘争心の差が出たのかな
I can't accept the result of this battle.
俺は絶対に納得できませんよ こんなバトル
We should request a rematch.
再戦を申し込むべきですよ
There's no way you'd
lose in normal conditions.
普通のコンディションなら 池田さんが負けるわけないし
How can you be so sure, Sakamoto ?
なぜそんなことが断言できるんだ 坂本
You might have to race in order to see it.
これは走った当事者同士にしか分からないことかもしれないが
Sure the road was wet, and the visibility
was the worst thanks to the fog.
確かに路面は濡れていたし
霧で視界は最悪だった
タイムを計ればレコードに遠く及ばないだろう
The time must have been far
slower than the course record.
だけど タイムに現れない内容に 俺は心から納得している
But I'm satisfied with the race's quality,
which can't be shown by just the time.
We used everything we had at
unimaginable speed in the fog.
あの霧の中ではありえないスピードで 俺たちは持ってる能力のすべてを出して戦った
I can't repeat such a miracle
battle even if I'm asked to.
もう一度やれと言われても 二度とできない
奇跡のようなあのバトルは一期一会だ
Such moments only come once.
That's why I'm satisfied.
だから俺は納得している
As long as we race on public streets,
the weather can't be an excuse.
ステージが公道であるかぎり どんな天候も言い訳にはできないだろう
This also means the Zero
theory is not perfect yet.
ゼロ理論もまだ完全なものじゃないということさ
Improvement begins with a realization like that.
それに気づくことから進歩が始まるんだ
I just have to keep improving
myself and my Zero theory.
進化させていけばいい 俺自身もゼロ理論もだ
How could he choose
the lead in this fog ?
この霧で先行はありえないだろう
Ikeda lost because of his strategy.
池田は作戦のミスだ
一本目は後ろで相手に目いっぱいプレッシャーをかけてやればいいんだ
In the first run, I'll just
put on pressure from behind.
If I'm lucky, my opponent will crash on his own.
うまくすりゃ自滅に追い込むことも可能だろう
Fog is that dangerous.
それほど霧は危険だからな
ゆっくり走るぶんにはどうってことはないが
It's nothing when you drive slowly, but once the pace
picks up, it's like walking on a wire between tall buildings.
ペースが上がれば高層ビルの綱渡りみたいなもんだぜ
In any case, I won't be the lead because
the chaser has a definite advantage.
ともかく先行はない 圧倒的に後追いが有利だからな
That was quite a
"meaty" hill climb, wasn't it ?
なかなか含蓄のあるヒルクライムでしたな
Very interesting.
実に面白い
まあな いやいや
Yeah, more or less.
Street battles are so deep.
公道バトルも奥が深い
That dramatic scenario could only be
equaled by top-category motor sports.
これはもうトップカテーゴリーのモータースポーツに匹敵するほどドラマッチクなシナリオでさ
I feel sorry for the gallery of spectators.
ただギャラリーはかわいそうですな
情報がなければ何が起こってるのかもわからんでしょうし
Without any info, they don't
know what's going on.
Quite literally, you can't see anything.
文字通り何も見えへんわけですから
What a shame, because the upcoming
downhill will be even more impressive.
これから始まるダウンヒルは さらに衝撃的なものになるっちゅのに
They chose to be the chaser.
向こうは後追いを選んできたぞ
I see.
そうか
Let me give you some
advice on pace management.
ペース配分だけ指示するぞ
Visibility is poor, so go at
80% right after the start.
視界が悪いからな
スタート直後は８０パーセント リズムが掴めてきたら９０に上げて
Once you pick up the rhythm, raise it to 90%
and when you're confident, go full throttle.
いけると思ったところで 全開だ
分かりました そのタイミングはどこまでに
I see. How long should
I wait for that timing ?
No more than one-third of the course.
Finish it off before that.
三分の一以上は持たせるな
それ以内でケリをつけろ
カウント始めるぞ ５ ４ ３ ２ １ ごー
I'm starting the count down.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Go !
It's begun.
始まりましたな
Is that so ?
そうですか  はい 伝えておきます
Okay, I'll tell him.
As you expected, the yellow car won.
シンちゃんの予想通り 黄色い車が勝っちゃったって
Two cars are coming down the hill, and
Hojo said you should pay attention to them.
もうすぐダウンヒルの二台が来るから
注目しておくようにって 北条さんが
To be honest...
本当は僕 全然興味ないんだけどな
...I'm not interested, at all.
Here they come.
来たよ
I saw wings.
羽が見えたね
Huh ? Wings ?
えっ 羽
先頭の 白い車に
On the white one in the lead.
８６に ウイングなんかついてなかったわよ
On the Eight-Six ?
It didn't have a wing.
No, I didn't mean that.
いや そういうのじゃなくて
I saw...
見えたんだ 鳥みたいな白い羽が
...white wings like on birds.
Alright, I can do this.
よし いける  遅いわけではないが想像していたほど早いわけでもない
He's not slow, but not as fast as I thought.
It's only natural because of the fog.
それはそうだろう この霧だからな
I'm gonna give you a hard time by
putting pressure on you from behind.
このまま背中からプレッシャーをかけていじめてやるぜ
後追いは絶対正解なんだ
I was absolutely right when
I chose to be the chaser.
スタート前に藤原に何か言ってたろう
You told Fujiwara something
before the start, didn't you ?
What's your strategy ?
どんな作戦を考えてるんだ
It's not exactly a strategy. Fujiwara
can win thanks to these conditions.
作戦というほどの作戦はないんだ
このコンディションなら 藤原は勝てる
えっ それじゃ何を
Then what did you tell him ?
An instruction about not giving too much data to our opponent. My mind is already on the next race.
敵に多くのデータを与えないための指示だ
俺の心はもう先にいる
You mean the final battle against Sidewinder ?
つまり サイドワインダーとの最終戦か
Yeah, you could say that.
まぁ そんなところかな
それの手前にもう一つ 俺だけのバトルがある
But before that, I have a battle of my own.
He picked up the pace.
ペースを上げてきやがった
Even though he's not a local, he can
see the course in this poor visibility.
地元でもないくせに この視界が悪い中でコースが見えてやがる
This isn't about technique.
He's got good driving sense.
テクニックがどうこうじゃない センスのいいヤツだぜ
だけど こんなペースじゃ長くは持たねえだろう
But he won't be able to
continue this pace for very long.
Even that tough Ikeda lost his concentration.
あのタフな池田でさえ集中力が切れたんだ
Keep trying as hard as you like.
ぜいぜい引っ張ってもらうぜ
必ず後半にミスが出る
You'll make a mistake in the second half.
That's when I'll make my move.
その時が勝負だ
俺に言わされば こんな勝負 結果はやる前から分かりきってるんだ
If you ask me, I'd say the result was
obvious even before the race began.
But the opponent's car is so well-tuned.
でも 相手の車はすごい完成度ですよ
I'm a Silvia owner myself,
so I can tell by just looking.
俺もシルビアユーザーだけに 見ただけで分かるんです
I think the balance of turning, braking, and
acceleration are better than Fujiwara's Eight-Six.
曲がる止まる加速するっていう三つのバランスは
藤原の８６より確実に上だと思います
Normally, he'd be at a disadvantage.
普通に考えたら かなり劣勢のはずなんですけど
What do you mean by "normally" ?
普通ってどんな状況だ
Like driving on a circuit on a sunny day ?
天気のいい日にサーキットみたいなところで走ったらってことか
If that's the case, vehicle
potential makes a difference.
それなら確かに車の差はでかい
だけど こんなコンディションになっちまったら
But in conditions like these,
it's all about the driver.
もう１００パーセントドライバーなんだよ
My brother's blind training was inspired
from Fujiwara's natural cluelessness.
兄貴が考えたブラインドトレーニングも元はといえば藤原の天然ボケがヒントだし
Not just visibility, but as all
the conditions deteriorate...
視界も含めてコンディションが悪化すればするほど藤原ゾーンのすごみは際立っていくんだ
...the Fujiwara zone gets refined.
憎らしいほどにな
So much so that I hate it.
いつも同じことを言うけどな ケンタ
I keep telling you the same
thing over and over, Kenta.
峠で一番恐ろしいドライバーは アイツなんだ
The most fearsome mountain pass driver is...
...him.
The way this guy's stomping
on the accelerator is scary.
恐ろしいぜ コイツのアクセルの踏みっぷりは
This speed feels twice or even three
times faster because of the poor visibility.
これだけ視界が不自由だとスピードの感覚が二倍にも三倍にも感じるんだ
どういう神経構造だ
What kind of nerves does he have ?
The next turn is a right-hand hairpin.
この先は右のヘアピン
やる気かよ
Is he challenging me to a braking
battle even in visibility as bad as this ?
このコンディションで 視界ぎりぎりのブレーキングバトルを
No thanks. Nobody can be sure
whether he'd wreck his car or not.
冗談じゃねぇ
自爆しないって保証はどこにある
巻き添えはごめんだぜ
I don't want to be involved.
Even if I fall behind a little during braking, I should be able to recover my loss during acceleration.
たとえブレーキングで少しぐらい離されても この車の戦闘力なら
立ち上がりでカバーできるはずだ
I'm not going with you. Go ahead and
disappear from the course alone.
ここは付き合わねえぜ
あわよくば 一人でコースから消えてくれ
You went in way too fast !
You won't be able to turn like that !
突っ込み過ぎだろう
そんなじゃ曲がれねぇ
なんだそりゃ
What the hell...?!
Is my sense of speed dull because of the fog ?
霧のせいで俺のスピード感覚鈍ってんのか
ここで慌てないことが肝心なんだ
What's important is not to
panic in a situation like this.
ホイルスピンをさせずに きっちりとアクセルを入れれば
If I accelerate precisely while minimizing
wheel-spin, the car will narrow the gap by itself.
車のほうが勝手に差を詰めてくれる
そこまでの車に仕上げてあるんだ
My car is tuned to do exactly that.
Even if I don't take a risky gamble, if I keep driving so I won't lose, victory will end up in my hands regardless.
一か八かのギャンブルをしなくても
負けない走りを続けていけば 最後に勝てる
He's fast. What happened ?!
速い
何が起こった
そんな馬鹿なことがあるか
This's ridiculous !
あれは４WDか
Is that a 4WD ?!
消えた
It disappeared...
本当にコースから
It really disappeared from the course !
消えちまいやがった
Alright !
よしゃ
危険なコンディションなのは 自分で走ったから分かっていたけど
I knew the conditions were dangerous
because I drove the course myself.
But Okuyama isn't a weak driver
who would be affected by the fog.
奥山は霧ぐらいでどうにかなるほど 柔なドライバーじゃない
チームのナンバーツーだしな
After all, he's our team's number two driver.
I knew he'd be able to
finish the race safely.
無事に走リ切るという確信はあった
But at the same time, I was sure he
wouldn't be able to win no matter what.
だけど 絶対に勝てないという確信もまた同時にあった
The reason why I let him
race without any advice...
それでも敢えてアドバイスもしないでやらせたのは
...is because I thought he'd gain an experience
he'd never be able to have otherwise.
二度とできないほどの貴重な体験をさせてやれると思ったからさ
He must be shocked since everything
he's built has crumbled, but...
今まで築きあげてきたものが根底から崩れるほどのショックだろうが
...that will definitely help Okuyama grow.
それが確実に奥山を成長させてくれる
This frustration will drive
him up to the next level.
この悔しさが 次のステップに登っていくための原動力になるんだ
Oh man, is this what they mean
by getting bewitched by a fox ?
やれやれ 狐につままれたというのはこういうことですな
Both Ikeda and Okuyama got defeated while
we're still trying to figure out what happened.
わけが分からんうちに 池田も奥山もやられてしまいましたわ
This is a big miscalculation for our recon team.
うちの偵察部隊にとっても大誤算です
We couldn't even learn half of what
we wanted because of the fog.
この霧のせいで 拾おう思ってたデータが半分もおさえられませんでした
Takahashi Ryosuke seems
to be lucky. I don't like that.
付きがありますな 高橋涼介という男
嫌な感じですわ
He can bring luck to his side
because he's so well prepared.
ふん 付きは見方にできるのはそれなりの準備ができているからだろう
You look happy, Hojo.
嬉しそうですな  北条はんは
Of course I am.
そりゃ嬉しいね
This festivity will finally reach the climax.
祭りはいよいよクライマックスだ
A stage we could never have even wished
for has been prepared for us after all.
ねがってもないステージが 俺たちのために準備されたわけだからな
Oh, I've been waiting for you, Takumi !
待ってたぞ 拓海
続いてるな 快進撃
Looks like you keep winning.
I have tons of things
I want to hear from you.
聞きたいこと山ほどあるよ
Spiral's car for the
downhill was an S15, right ?
スパイラルの下りはS１５だったんだって
What was the car like ? Was it tough ?
どんな車だった
手ごわかったか
Well, actually the course was covered in fog,
and the surface was partially wet, so...
いや それが
今回はコースに霧が出ちゃってて
おまけに路面も中途半端に濡れてたし
...the car looked quite powerful, but the conditions
didn't allow the driver to step on the gas very hard.
相当パワーのありそうな車だったけど
アクセル踏み切れる状況じゃなっかたから
霧が出ても決行するんだ
You still race, even in the fog ?
It's a street racing rule that we race in any
condition so long as both teams agree to participate.
バトルって お互いが納得すれば どんな状況でもやるのが公道ルールなんですけど
This time, we were lucky because
our opponent accepted our challenge.
今回は相手が受けてくれてラッキーでしたよ
そうだよな 仕切り直しって言われても
You may be right.
It'd be a pain for you guys to drive all
the way from Gunma for another day.
群馬から遠いところまで出っばていくほうは大変だもんな
That's true, but what I really meant was...
そういう意味もあるんですけど
俺としてはコンディションがちょっと悪いほうが集中力が出るんで
...I didn't want the race to be canceled because
I tend to focus better when the conditions are severe.
中止になってほしくないって思ってたんですよ
Just like I said, right, Senpai ?
やっぱり俺が言った通りでしょ 先輩
Yeah.
いや あの日はこっちも雨が降ってさ
It rained over here that day.
Kenji and I were worried
about the weather in Hakone.
ケンジと二人で箱根の天気を心配していたんだ
そうしたら雨はむしろ拓海にとっては有利だって イツキが自信満々に断言したんだよ
But Itsuki stated that rain would give you an
advantage. He was confident about that.
Ahem !
Still, it feels like you've really
hit the moment of truth.
それにしても 来るべきところまで来たって感じだよな
You've accomplished something great.
The next one is the final battle.
途方もない快挙だよ
ついに最終戦だぞ
Even the high-level Kanagawa
racers are no match for Project D.
あの超ハイレベルの神奈川もプロジェクトDの前では 形無しですからね クー
そうそう 減給覚悟で社長に直談判した結果
Even though we were afraid of a salary cut,
we still asked the boss for a day off.
Both of us are going to
take a vacation that week.
俺たち二人とも その週に休みをもらえることになったからさ
I'm already so excited !
クー 今から気合入りばかりですよね
All of the Speed Stars members
will come watch your race.
スピードスターズのメンバー全員で 応援に行くからな
伝説が生まれる瞬間に立ち合うことができると信じてるよ
I believe we'll witness the birth of a legend.
How is it ?
どうです
さすがだよ 完璧な仕事だ
Just like you. Your work is perfect.
I can't feel the benefit of the wing on the streets of Akagi,
but I really wanted stability in high speed corners.
ウイングの真価は赤木道路では実感できないけど
高速コーナーでのスタビリティがとにかくほしかった
All that's left is how well I can
manage this car after a little hiatus.
後は俺自身がどこまでコイツに対応できるかだな
ブランクもあるし
Ryosuke, do you really have to do this ?
涼介さん どうしてもやらなきゃいけないことですか
I wouldn't say anything if the
opponent was someone else, but...
他の相手なら何も言いませんが こればっかりは
The next one will be the final away race for Project D.
If something happens to you, we can't redo this.
プロジェクトDの遠征もいよいよファイナルだし
涼介さんにもしものことがあったら 取り返しがつかないっていうか
You shouldn't do this.
This isn't like you, Ryosuke.
やめるべきですよ
涼介さんらしくないじゃないですか
すまんな 松本  これは俺にとって 避けて通れない関門なんだ
Sorry, Matsumoto, but this is a fate I can't avoid.
あの人を放っておくわけにはいかない
I can't leave that person as he is.
This is something only I can do.
俺にしかできない役目なんだ
It's difficult to settle the next battle, but don't worry. I'll return no matter what.
落としどころの難しいバトルだけど 心配するな
俺は必ず戻ってくる
そこまで言うんでしたら
If you insist...
I have one condition.
一つだけ条件があります
Huh ? Are you joking ?
はあ 嘘だろう
No, it's true, Keisuke.
本当なんですよ 啓介さん
Someone saw Ryosuke and his FC here.
ここで涼介さんとFCを見たヤツがいるんです
Plus the FC had a huge wing.
しかもそのFCにでっかいウイングがついてたって言うんですよ
A wing ?
ウイング
That's strange.
Was it really my brother ?
それは変だろう
本当に兄貴なのか
He said he saw his face
clearly, so I'm sure of it.
はっきりと顔を見たって言うから  間違いないです
An Akagi street racer wouldn't
mistake anyone else for Ryosuke.
赤木道路の走り屋が涼介さんと別のヤツを間違えるなんて  ありえないっすよ
確かにここんとこ  ガレージに兄貴の車を見かけないと思ってたけど
I was thinking that I hadn't seen my
brother's car in the garage from time to time.
If that's true, why does he need a wing ?
それが本当だとしたら
何のためにウイングなんか
I have a bad feeling.
嫌な予感がする
Hakone's fog is nice.
いいよな  箱根の霧は
It hides the dirty side of reality.
薄汚れた現実をすべてかき消してくれる
When I stand still like this, there's
nothing other than absolute silence...
こうして佇んでいれば
そこにあるのは絶対的な静寂
...and overwhelming loneliness.
そうして圧倒的な孤独だ
This is the state of nirvana, right, Kaori ?
涅槃とはこんなところかもしれないな 香織
Ever since I lost you, I feel like
I've been standing in the fog.
お前を失ってから  俺はいつも霧の中に佇んでいるようなものだ
I'm going to have a race against
Ryosuke where we both bet our lives.
ここで俺は涼介と命の遣り取りをする
I'll send one of us to your side.
俺たち二人のうちどちらかを  お前の傍に送ってやるよ
So make a choice.
選ぶのはお前だ
This time, follow your heart, Kaori.
今度こそ本音で選ぶんだぜ 香織
Fujiwara Takumi:
Takahashi Ryosuke:
Takahashi Keisuke:
Ikeda Ryuji:
Okuyama Hiroya:
Hojo Gou:
Kubo Eiji:
Matsumoto:
Miki Shinichiro
Koyasu Takehito
Seki Tomokazu
Nakai Kazuya
Sakaguchi Shuhei
Kiuchi Hidenobu
Kase Yasuyuki
Nishi Ryotaro
Yuugure ni kawaranai keshiki
日の暮れに 変わらない景色
Takeuchi Itsuki:
Iketani Koichiro:
Kenta:
Fumihiro:
Inui Shinji:
Shinji's Mom:
Iwata Mitsuo
Yao Kazuki
Okano Kosuke
Hosoi Hajime
Abe Atsushi
Hirose Yuuka
Furikaeru tadottekita michi
振り返る 辿ってきた道
Setsunasa mo, yorokobi mo, kienai itami mo
切なさも 喜びも 消えない痛みも
Kazoetetara kiri ga nai ne to hitori aruku
数えてたら限がないねと独り歩く
A
Central Anime
Production
Translation:
Hiro-kun
Timing:
Todd Perkins
Editing:
Lillian-Hime
Barbara
Todd Perkins
Brain
Dave
Mouse
Steve S.
Nomake
Kazoekirenai hodo no zanzo
数え切れないほどの残像 ギャンブル生き抜いてきた残党
Gambaru ikinuite kita zattou
Toki ni tatakai toki ni wakari ai
時に戦い 時に解りあい きれい事ばかりじゃなかった真実
Kireigoto bakari ja nakatta shinjitsu
Shotta mama arata na ippo
背負ったまま新たな一歩
Akane gumo ga machi wo someru
あかね雲が街を染める この行く先をそっと問いかけて見る
Kono yuku saki wo sotto toitakete miru
空はなにもいわず だけど私にこの道を照らしている
Sora wa nani mo iwazu
Dakedo watashi ni kono michi wo terashiteiru
透き通る景色を感じて
Sukitooru keshiki wo kanjite
Senritsu wo yuuhi ga kanadete
旋律を夕陽が奏で
Sukitooru keshiki wo kanjite
透き通る景色を感じて
Senritsu wo yuuhi ga kanadete
旋律を夕陽が奏で